and now we move on to the next award
segmenta General Insurance company in
motor claims and here comes the envelope
for you
sir so most Innovative General Insurance
company in motor claims the award goes
to IC
lomard congratulations to IC Lombard
General Insurance Company Limited for
winning the most Innovative General
Insurance company in motor claims
division accepting the award we have Raj
manani and the entire team of IC Lombard
General Insurance Company
[Music]
Limited
uh thanks everyone uh thanks sinx and
lumik for uh this
beautiful uh event and uh the message is
this is just a uh I mean beginning we
have long way to reach and uh as Say by
Mur sir we'll be you know uh happy to
see all of all everyone has insurance by
2047 thank
you congratulations once again ladies
and gentlemen I said winning the most
Innovative General in claims division
congratulations and very well deserved